https://www.photographer.com.au/copyright#privacy

Terms of Use
© Copyright Robert Edwards Robert Edwards retains copyright on all content including images, videos, graphics and text as enforced under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, in addition to Australian and international copyright laws. This means that you must not distribute the content to others, modify or re-use them without the express written permission of Robert Edwards. Robert Edwards reserves all rights.
Warning: Copyright interests are vigorously protected. When an infringement is discovered you will be notified and invoiced the industry-standard triple fee for unauthorised usage and/or prosecuted for Copyright Infringement in an Australian court where you will be subject to paying Statutory Damages in the amount of US$150,000 as well as our court costs and attorneys’ fees with the possibility of up to five years imprisonment.
Limit of LiabilityThe information, text, photographs, graphics, and links provided herein are provided as a convenience however Robert Edwards does not warrant the accuracy, or completeness of the information, text, graphics, links, and other items contained on this server or any other server. Use of this web site is at your own risk.
PrivacyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a payment from www.photographer.com.au (the “Site”).
Personal Information We CollectWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet Service Provider, search query, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
When you make a payment through the Site we do not collect any information about you. Your name, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and invoice number is handled through Stripe. We refer to this information as “Payment Information.”
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Payment Information.
How Do We Use Your Personal Information?We use the Payment Information that we collect generally to fulfil any payments placed through the Site including processing your payment information. Additionally may we use this Payment Information to communicate with you via email to issue a receipt and to screen payments for potential risk or fraud.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimise our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
Sharing Your Personal InformationWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Stripe to power our online payment gateway. You can read more about how Stripe uses your Personal Information here: https://stripe.com/au/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
Do Not TrackPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
Your RightsIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfil contracts we might have with you (for example if you make a payment through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Australia and the USA.
Data RetentionWhen you place a payment through the Site, we will maintain your Payment Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
ChangesWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
Contact UsFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at re@photographer.com.au or by mail at PO Box 1100 North Sydney, NSW 2059 Australia.
As of May 2018. Subject to change without notice.
